{
    "id": "8715405b93a642fa90ec3af104552742",
    "title": "Past Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. TV when the lights went out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "was watching",
                "had watched"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c5bbc667f4243beb593c16492baa121"
        },
        {
            "question": "The patient …………………. before the doctor arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "was dying",
                "had died"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "22f27116ad854aa0b96c71006ed17b1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "His father ……………….. last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "was dying",
                "has died",
                "had died"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "677c9763c3ce4403b719f41b4ea861d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly I realized that I ……………… him before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "had met",
                "have met"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17929d7a13bf4a99a07aa14666bc39fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… in the garage when James turned up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "working",
                "worked",
                "was working",
                "have been working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "43f50a8755044fdd8d32805b4679421a"
        },
        {
            "question": "While you were playing I ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worked",
                "was working",
                "have worked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2e0d8fd0d1a74ea2a69a011a53aff711"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I ……………….. the window, the cat jumped out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was opening",
                "opened",
                "have opened",
                "had opened"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e6870a01c8f4ea69ac1832ef697cc6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………… in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "started",
                "have started",
                "were starting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d6f668869e146b995b10a0ae5f8a863"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ……………….. not come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9324453c5e214fc8bd1cc614ad7e0c74"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked if I …………………. help him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5ec9a3d6421142da90f546dbed6e6f5d"
        }
    ]
}